Guide to the Larry LaRocco Collection 1982-1994
Boise State University Library, Special Collections and Archives
- Coeur d'Alene office, 6
  - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Discrimination; Harassment
  - Eagle Scout Letters, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - East Shoshone Water District, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Economic Development Agency (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Shoshone County; Economic Adjustment Assistance; Clearwater County
  - Education, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Education; Goals 2000; Homeschooling
  - Energy Fuels, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Ethanol; Fuel
  - Education-School List, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Commencements-Speeches, Addresses, Etc.
  - Elizabeth Park, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Coeur d'Alene River; Water Pollution
  - Fair Market Housing, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    Idaho--Housing
  - Farmers Home Administration, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Fernan Ranger District, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Festival at Sandpoint, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    Sandpoint, Idaho; Arts
  - Fly/Mosquito Timber Sale, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    Timber Harvests; Coeur d'Alene National Forest
  - Forest Stewardship Legislation, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    Panhandle National Forest
  - Federal Communication Commission, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    Religious Freedom
  - Foreign Aid, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    Economic Assistance; Idaho--International Trade; Russia--Economic Assistance
  - GATT-World Trade Organization, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Grizzly Bear Recovery, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    Grizzly Bears; Panhandle National Forest; Priest Lake, Idaho; Flathead National Forest
  - Gulf USA: Pension List, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    Bunker Hill; Superfund; Coeur d'Alene Basin; Mines and Mining--Environmental Aspects
  - Gun Control, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    Crime Control Act; National Rifle Association
  - Health Issues, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    Medical Care; National Health Care; Rural Health Care
  - Health Care, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    Idaho Medical Communication; Health Care Plan--Constituent Communication; Rural Health Care
  - Hecla Mining Company, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    Coeur d'Alene Indians
    Brown, Arthur
  - Highways, State Transportation, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Idaho Transportation Department; Roads
  - Homeless: North Idaho Committee Service, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Idaho Citizens Network, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    Bunker Hill Superfund--Constituent Communication; Pollution--Heavy Metals; Lead Poisoning; Mines and Mining--Environmental Aspects
    Miller, Barbara; Sjogren, Sylvia
  - Idaho Council on Industry and the Environment, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Idaho Housing Agency, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    Homelessness
  - Idaho Industrial Committee, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Idaho Nuclear Energy Laboratory, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    INEL; Thyroid Cancer; Radiation Poisoning
  - Inland Empire Public Lands Council, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    Public Lands; Timber Sales; Panhandle National Forest; Fernan Ranger District
  - Intermountain Forest Industry Association, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    Forest Service; Timber Industry
  - Invitations, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Kiebert Group, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    Coeur d'Alene Basin; Water Pollution; Pollution--Heavy Metals; Mines and Mining--Environmental
  - Kellogg Development Project, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Kootenai-Benewah Medical Society (Box 2, Folder 44)
    Kootenai County--Medical Care
  - Kootenai County Human Rights Task Force, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    Human Rights; Discrimination; Racism; Aryan Nations; Neo-Nazism; White Supremacists
  - Kootenai County: Water Resources, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    Kootenai County--Water Resources; Coeur d'Alene Lake
  - Kootenai Electric Cooperative: Youth Activities, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    Kootenai County
  - Kootenai Environmental Alliance, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    Kootenai County; Coeur d'Alene Basin
    Manley, Art
  - Kootenai Indian Tribe, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    Kootenai Indians
  - Kootenai River Erosion, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    Kootenai River--Erosion; Boundary County
  - Kootenai Sturgeon, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    Kootenai River; Upper Columbia United Tribes; Kootenai Indians
  - Kootenai Sturgeon, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    Kootenai River; Kootenai Indians
  - Kootenai Sturgeon, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Labor, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Labor Unions
  - United States Department of Labor, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Mines and Mining; Shoshone County; Dislocated Worker Program; Job Training
  - Lake Users Association, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Coeur d'Alene Lake
  - Lake Pend Oreille Pool Level, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Coeur d'Alene Basin; Sandpoint Idaho; Lake Pend Oreille--Fisheries
  - Lake Pend Oreille Pool Level, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Sandpoint Idaho; Lake Pend Oreille--Fisheries; Salmon; Lake Pend Oreille--Constituent Communication; Army Corps of Engineers; Columbia River System
  - Lake Pend Oreille Pool Level, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Sandpoint Idaho; Lake Pend Oreille--Fisheries; Drawdowns; Lake Pend Oreille--Constituent Communication; Columbia River System
  - Lake Pend Oreille Drawdown, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Sandpoint Idaho; Lake Pend Oreille--Fisheries; Drawdowns
  - Land Exchanges, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Lakes Protection, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Coeur d'Alene Lake; Lake Spokane
  - Louisiana-Pacific Corporation, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Mallard-Larkin (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Idaho--Wilderness Areas; Clearwater National Forest; Panhandle National Forest
  - Mining, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Mines and Mining; Shoshone County; Persian Gulf Medal; Silver Mining; Bunker Hill Mine; Coeur d'Alene Basin--Mines and Mining
  - Mining, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Hecla Mining; Clarks Fork River; Coeur d'Alene Basin--Mines and Mining
  - Milo Creek, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Mullan-Plummer Rail Line, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - North American Free Trade Agreement, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    NAFTA
  - National Federation of Federal Employees, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - National and Community Service (Includes Youth Service), 1994 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    Americorps
  - National Home Builders Association (Box 3, Folder 19)
    Campaign 1994
  - National Public Lands Council, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - National Youth Leaders Conference: Alumni From Idaho, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    Congressional Youth Leadership
  - Natural Resource Trustees, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    Idaho--Natural Resources; Mines and Mining--Environmental Aspects; Coeur d'Alene Basin
  - National Endowment for the Arts (Box 3, Folder 23)
    Idaho Commission on the Arts
  - Navy-Intermediate Scale Measurement System, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    Lake Pend Oreille--Environmental Aspects; Department of the Navy
  - North Idaho Lake Association Coalition, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    Coeur d'Alene Basin; Water Pollution
  - North Idaho Community Express, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Northwest Power Planning Council, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    Kokanee Salmon; Lake Pend Oreille
  - North Idaho Rural Health Consortium, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - One Percent Initiative, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - One Percent Initiative, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    Idaho Property Tax
  - Panhandle Area Council, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Pacific Gas Transmission, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    Gas--Pipelines
  - Pack River Road, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    Bonner County--Roads
  - People for the West, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Private Industry Council, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    Small Business Administration; Job Training
  - Plum Creek Company, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Plummer-Mullan Tourist Train, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    Idaho--Tourist Trade
  - Panhandle Forest Information, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Panhandle Health District, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Priest River, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    Priest River, Idaho
  - Proposition One, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    Idaho Citizens Alliance; Homosexuality; Anti-Gay Initiative
  - Post Falls Chamber of Commerce, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Potlatch-Bureau of Land Management, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    Idaho--Public Lands; Arkansas--Public Lands; Potlatch
  - Pro Choice, 1992-1994 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    Abortion; Campaign, 1994
  - Priest River, City of, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Railways (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Resource Conservation and Development, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    Idaho--Soil Conservation District; Natural Resources
  - Resumes, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Rochet Creek Water, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    Safe Drinking Water Act; St. Maries, Idaho
  - Rural Development Agency, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Salmon Summit, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 51)
    Chaney, Ed
  - Sandpoint, Idaho, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Scott Salvage Sale, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 53)
    Salmon; Timber Sales
  - Shoshone County, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 54)
    St. Joe River
  - Silver Valley Heritage Project, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    Historic Preservation; Wallace, Idaho; Kellogg, Idaho
  - Silver Valley Economic Development Corporation, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    Wallace, Idaho; Kellogg, Idaho
  - Silver Valley Development, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Silver--Mines and Mining; Mines and Mining--Environmental Aspects; Timber Industry--Environmental Aspects; Wallace, Idaho; Miners--Job Training
  - Silver Valley Task Force, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Silver--Mines and Mining; Mines and Mining--Environmental Aspects; Pollution--Heavy Metal; Wallace, Idaho; Miners--Job Training; Kellogg, Idaho
    Magnuson, Harry
  - Small Loggers Council, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Solid Waste, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Landfills
  - Special Recognition, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Spokane Aquifer Protection, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Rathdrum--Spokane Aquifer; Idaho--Water Quality
  - Spokane Chamber, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Spokane, Washington; Forest Service
  - Spokane River-Hayen Sewer, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    Spokane River; Water Quality
  - Small Governments: Environmental Protection Agency, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    Spokane River; Water Quality; Landfills
  - Superfund Site, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    Bunker Hill Superfund; Mines and Mining--Environmental Aspects; Kellogg, Idaho
  - Superfund Site, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Bunker Hill Superfund; Kellogg, Idaho; Wallace, Idaho; Mines and Mining--Environmental Aspects
  - Superfund Site, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - St. Joe Valley Development Foundation, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    Timber Industry; Coeur d'Alene Indians; St. Joe River
  - St. Joe Erosion, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Taft Tunnel, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    Wallace, Idaho; Biking Trails; Tourist Trade
  - Taft Tunnel, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    Wallace, Idaho; Biking Trails; Tourist Trade; Milwaukee Railroad
  - Taft Tunnel, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    Taft Tunnel; Biking Trails; Tourist Trade; Route of the Hiawatha
  - Taft Tunnel Preservation Society, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    Biking Trails; Tourist Trade; Wallace, Idaho; Shoshone County
  - Taft Tunnel Preservation Society, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    Biking Trails; Tourist Trade; Wallace, Idaho
  - Taft Tunnel Meeting File, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Term Limitation, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    Elected Officials--Term Limits
  - Twin Lakes, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    Rathdrum, Idaho; Clean Lakes Coordinating Council
  - Timber Issues, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    Timber Industry--Environmental Aspects; Forest Reserves
  - Timber Issues, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    Timber Industry--Environmental Aspects; Forest Reserves; Timber Industry--Idaho--Surveys
  - Tourist Train, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    Tourist Trade; Coeur d'Alene Indians
  - United We Stand, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Union Pacific--Wallace Line, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    Union Pacific Railroad; Wallace, Idaho; Idaho Public Utilities Commission; Kellogg, Idaho
  - Union Pacific--Wallace Line, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    Union Pacific Railroad; Wallace, Idaho; Idaho Public Utilities Commission; Kellogg, Idaho; Hecla Mining Company
  - Union Pacific, Wallace Line, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    Union Pacific Railroad; Wallace, Idaho; Interstate Commerce Commission; Kellogg, Idaho; Idaho Public Utilities Commission
  - United States Forest Service, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - United States Forest Service, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - United States Forest Service, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - United States Forest Service: Labor Issue, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Forest Reserves--Constituent Communication; Forest Health
  - Veterans Affairs: Information, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Agent Orange Assistance Program; Vietnam Veterans
  - Veterans, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Wallace Chamber of Commerce, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Waterways Association, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Washington Water Power, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Wetlands: Refuge, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    Wetlands; National Wildlife Refuge System
  - Wilderness: Public Meetings, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    Timber Industry; Wilderness Areas--Constituent Communication; Forest Reserves--Constituent Communication
    Statement on Wilderness Dec 14-16, 1992
  - Wilderness: Public Meetings, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    Wilderness Areas--Constituent Communication; Forest Reserves
  - Congressional Research Service, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Federal Express, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Flag Requests, 1990-1992 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Flag Orders, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - General Services Administration: Supply Orders, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - House Documents: Room Legislature, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Inventory: Furniture and Equipment, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Journal Vouchers, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Lease: 408 Sherman, Ste.206, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Mail Log, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Mail: Procedures/Log, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Office Budget, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Presidential Greetings: Birthday/Anniversary, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Presidential Greetings/Photographs, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Schedule Requests, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Vouchers: Blank and Completed, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Vouchers: Blank and Completed, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Vouchers: Blank and Completed, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - White House Tours, Etc., 1994 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Lewiston office, 7
  Lewiston, Idaho is located between the Snake and Clearwater River adjacent to several national forests. The city's economic reliance on natural resources is evident in the files collected by LaRocco's regional staff. Though such issues as health care and clean water are discussed in the papers, dominate throughout the series are materials about the environment.
  The efforts to save the salmon from extinction are well documented here. Drawdowns on the Lower Granite and Dworshak drew negative reactions from area residents. Petitions against the action can be found in Box 1, Folder 15. Files 19-26 in Box 2 pertain directly to the salmon. They contain publications from public and private organizations evaluating the situation, and, communications from public officials and private citizens. Public opinions pertaining to the environment are found throughout the files.
  Debates concerning the addition of wilderness areas to Idaho are found in the boxes. Lewiston is a timber town and directly affected by logging restrictions and changes in governmental policies. Documentation of timber, mining and recreational concerns are in the Idaho Wilderness files.
  Box 3 contains the general files for the office. Included in these is information and feedback from the town meetings on health care.
  - Alliance for America, 1991-1993 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Endangered Species Act; Forest Reserves; Timber Industry
  - American Association of Crop Insurers, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Americans With Disabilities Act, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Bonneville Power Administration, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Bureau of Land Management, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - City Council, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    City Government; Lewiston, Idaho--Elections, 1991; Idaho--Elections, 1991
  - Clearwater Economic Development Association, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Clearwater County; Timber Industry
  - Clearwater Resource Coalition, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Clearwater County
  - Clearwater Resource Conservation Development, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Clearwater County; Idaho Rural Development Council
  - Communication Network, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Information Networks
  - Constituent Mail: Salmon Issue plus Drawdown, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Drawdowns; Constituent Communication; Snake River; Columbia River
  - Constituent Mail, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Department of Employment, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Department of Environmental Quality, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Department of Environmental Quality; Riggins Hot Springs
  - Drawdown Lower River Granite, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Drawdowns; Lower Granite Reservoir; Salmon--Constituent Communication
  - Drawdown Lower River Granite, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Drawdown Lower River Granite, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Dworshak Drawdown, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Drawdowns; Dworshak Dam; Salmon--Constituent Communication
  - Dworshak Drawdown, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Dworshak Drawdown McGinty, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    McGinty, Kathleen
  - Dworshak Drawdown McGinty, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Dworshak Follow up, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Forest Service Law Enforcement Regulations, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Forest Reserves; Forest Service--Constituent Communication
  - Forest Service: Miscellaneous, 1992-1994 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Forest Reserves; Clearwater National Forest
  - Grizzly Bear/Wolf Recovery, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    Grizzly Bears; Wolves
  - Hells Canyon National Recreation Area, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Idaho Department of Lands, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    Idaho--Public Lands
  - Idaho Forest Management Act (I), 1988 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    McClure, James
  - Idaho Forest Management Act (II), 1988 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Forest Management
  - Idaho National Forests, undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Idaho Rural Health Education Center, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    Idaho--Medical Care Facilities
  - Idaho Wilderness, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Idaho Wilderness: Idaho Wildlife Summer, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Idaho--Wilderness
    LaRocco, Larry; Church, Frank; Trueblood, Ted
  - Idaho Wilderness: Maps, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Idaho Wilderness: Millard Larkins Proposal, undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
    Idaho--Wilderness Areas; Clearwater National Forest; Idaho--Forest Reserves
  - Idaho Wilderness: Mining, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    Mines and Mining; Idaho--Wilderness Areas
  - Idaho Wilderness: Miscellaneous, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Idaho Wilderness: Outfitters, 1991-1993 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    Idaho--Wilderness Areas; River Guides; Hunting Guides
  - Idaho Wilderness: Press Coverage, 1991-1993 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    Idaho--Wilderness Areas; Wilderness Areas--Mines and Mining
  - Idaho Wilderness: Resource Material, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Idaho Wilderness: River of No Return Wilderness Area, 1977-1993 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Trueblood, Ted; Day, Ernie; Bowler, Bruce; Church, Frank
  - Idaho Wilderness: Roadless Area, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Idaho Wilderness: Studies, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Idaho Wilderness: Sustainable Forest and Communities Act, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Testimony 8/26/1993
    H.R.1570; H.R.3732
  - Idaho Wilderness: Sustainable Forest and Communities Act, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Idaho--Wilderness Areas; Idaho--Forest Reserves
  - Interior Department, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Timber Salvage; Nez Perce National Forest; Department of the Interior; Geological Survey
  - Juliaetta, Idaho, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Water Quality
  - Labor Department, 1991-1993 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Labor Unions; Timber Industry
    H.R.3936
  - Latah County, 1998; 1991 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Lewis Clark State College, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Public Relations; Wilderness Areas
  - Lewiston Orchards Water, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Lewiston--Water Quality
  - Montana Wilderness, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Montana--Wilderness Areas
  - Lewiston Office: Monthly Report 1991 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Nez Perce Historical Park Additions Study, 1991-1993 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Nuclear Reactor, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    INEL; Nuclear Reactor
    Testimony at INEL May 28, 1991
  - Outfitters Issues, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    River Guides; Hunting Guides; Fishing Guides
  - Persian Gulf, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    Military Draft; Persian Gulf War
  - Roots, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Salmon Recovery, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Salmon Recovery, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Salmon Recovery, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Salmon Recovery, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Salmon Recovery, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Salmon Recovery, 1991-1993 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Salmon Recovery, 1992,1994 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Salmon Recovery Working Group, 1991,1992 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Timber Issues, 1989-1994 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Town Meetings/Persian Gulf, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    Persian Gulf War--Constituent Communication
  - Veterans Info, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Wild and Scenic Rivers - Salmon, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    Idaho--Public Lands; Forest Service
  - Aging Hearing, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Aged; Medical Care
  - Appalossa Horse Club (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Congressional Art Contest, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Gulf War: Faxes, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Health Care Meetings, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - High Risk Drivers Act, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Kamiah High School, 1993 April 29 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Commencement Speech
  - Lewis-Clark State College, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Nicholas, Hugh
  - Lewiston: Bryden Canyon Road, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Lewiston, Idaho--Roads
  - Lewiston Office Open House, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Lewiston Town Meeting, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Pre-Congressional, 8
  - Pre-Congressional
    Prior to his election to the House of Representatives in 1990, Larry LaRocco had ran for the position in 1982 against Larry Craig. He also challenged Boisean Jim Risch for a state legislative seat in 1986. LaRocco was defeated in both races. Series 8, Box 1, Folders 1 holds campaign material for these elections. Folder 2 contains copies of speeches from the 1984 campaign primarily from the National Democratic Convention.
    - Campaigns, 1982; 1986 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Campaign, 1984; Speeches (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Kootenai Environmental Group, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Idaho State Lottery
    The election year of 1988 brought gaming to the forefront of Idaho politics. LaRocco headed the committee for the passage of a referendum f establishing a State Lottery. The papers from Idahoans or the Lottery are retained in Box 1, Folders 4-14.
    - Evaluation of On-Line Wagering System..., 1988 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Consider (Anti-Lottery Organization), 1988 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: Pro-Lottery, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Media Correspondence, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Media Statements, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - News Releases, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Pro-Lottery Bumper sticker, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Public Gaming International, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Situational Analysis of Proposed Idaho Lottery, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - West Virginia Lotto Report, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Computer disks, 9